<resources>
    <!--These are strings unique to Tic-Tac-Toe-->
    <string name="app_name">Citadels</string>
    <string name="hello_world">coffee is just bean soup</string>

    <string name="ASSASSIN_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Assassin</string>
    <string name="ASSASSIN_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Call the name of another character whom you wish to kill.
When the killed character is called to take his turn, he must
remain silent and skip his entire turn for this round without
revealing his character card.</string>

    <string name="WITCH_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Witch</string>
    <string name="WITCH_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">First you must gather resources, then you must call the name
of another character whom you wish to bewitch, and then your
turn is put on hold. You cannot build at this time, and the only
district effects you can use are those that occur when gathering
resources (Gold Mine, Library, or Observatory).
When the bewitched character is called to take his turn, he
gathers resources and his turn immediately ends. He cannot
build a district or use any of his character’s abilities—not even
those that provide “extra” resources (like the Merchant’s extra
gold). The only district effects that the bewitched player can
use are those that occur when gathering resources.
Now you resume your turn as if you were playing the bewitched
character; you use that character’s abilities, including those that
provide extra resources, passive abilities (such as the Bishop’s
protection against rank 8 characters or the Architect’s increased
building limit), and restrictions (such as the Navigator’s inability
to build districts). You play with the cards in your hand, pay with
the gold in your stash, gain resources from districts in your city,
and build new districts in your city. You cannot use effects from
unique districts owned by the bewitched player.
If the Blackmailer is bewitched, you assign threat markers,
receive bribes from threatened players, and choose to reveal the
threat marker if the targeted player does not pay.
If the King or Patrician is bewitched, he still takes the crown. If
the Emperor is bewitched, you choose whom to give the crown
to and take the resource from that player.</string>

    <string name="MAGISTRATE_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Magistrate</string>
    <string name="MAGISTRATE_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Take the three warrant markers and assign them facedown
to three different character tokens of your choice. One of the
markers shows the signed warrant on its face; only the player
marked with the signed warrant is targeted.
If the targeted player pays to build a district during his turn,
you may reveal his warrant marker by flipping it faceup. If you
do, you confiscate that district from him and build it in your
city instead for free.
The confiscated district never enters the targeted player’s city,
but it does count toward the targeted player’s building limit for
the turn. The targeted player receives back all gold paid for that
district. If he is able to build more than one district during his
turn, you can confiscate only the first district he pays to build.
Note: You cannot confiscate a district if you have an identical
district (with the same name) already in your city.</string>

    <string name="THIEF_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Thief</string>
    <string name="THIEF_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Call the name of another character whom you wish to rob.
When a player reveals that character to take his turn, you
immediately take all of his gold.
You cannot rob the rank 1 character (Assassin, Witch, or
Magistrate), the killed character, or the bewitched character.</string>

    <string name="SPY_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Spy</string>
    <string name="SPY_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Choose another player and name a district type (noble,
religious, trade, military, or unique). Then look at the
cards in that player’s hand. For each card in his hand that
matches the named district type, take one gold from that
player’s stash and gain one card from the deck.
If the player whose hand you looked at has more cards of
matching districts than gold in his stash, you take all the gold
in his stash, and you still gain cards for each of the matching.
districts.</string>

    <string name="BLACKMAILER_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Blackmailer</string>
    <string name="BLACKMAILER_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Take the two threat markers and assign them facedown to two
different character tokens of your choice. One of the markers
shows the flowered lace on its face; both players are threatened,
but only the player marked with the flowered lace is targeted.
When a threatened player is called to take his turn, he must
immediately gather resources and then resolve the threat:
he can bribe you by giving you half his gold (rounded down),
which removes his threat marker without revealing it. A
threatened player with only one gold in his stash can bribe
you by giving you zero gold. If he does not bribe you, you may
reveal his threat marker by flipping it faceup. If you reveal the
flowered lace, you immediately take all his gold.
A threatened player must resolve the threat before he is able to use
any of his character abilities or build districts, and the only district
effects he can use before resolving the threat are those that occur
when gathering resources (Gold Mine, Library, or Observatory).
You cannot assign threat markers to the rank 1 character
(Assassin, Witch, or Magistrate), the killed character, or
the bewitched character. You can assign threat markers to
characters who have been assigned warrant markers.</string>

    <string name="MAGICIAN_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Magician</string>
    <string name="MAGICIAN_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You can do one of the following:
1. Exchange your entire hand of cards with another player’s
hand of cards; if you have zero cards in your hand, you
simply take the other player’s cards.
2. Discard any number of cards from your hand facedown
to the bottom of the district deck to gain an equal
number of cards from the district deck.</string>

    <string name="WIZARD_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Wizard</string>
    <string name="WIZARD_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Look at another player’s hand of cards and choose one of those
cards. Then either pay to immediately build the chosen card in
your city or add it to your hand. If you immediately build it,
it does not count toward your building limit, which means you
can build another district this turn.
During this turn, you can build districts that are identical to any
other district already in your city.</string>

    <string name="SEER_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Seer</string>
    <string name="SEER_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Take a card at random from each other player’s hand and add
those cards to your hand. Then give one card from your hand
to each player you took a card from. If a player has no cards in
hand, you neither take a card from him nor give him a card.
Taken cards can be kept and given back in several different
combinations: you can give a player the exact same card back,
you can give a card taken from one player to another, or you can
keep a card taken and give back a card from your original hand.
Your building limit this turn is two.</string>

    <string name="KING_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">King</string>
    <string name="KING_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one gold for each noble district in your city.
At some point during your turn, you must take the crown. You
are now the crowned player, so you call characters for the rest
of the round, and you will be the first to choose a character
during the next round (until another player chooses the King).
If you are killed, you skip your turn like any other character.
At the end of the round, reveal the King’s character card and
take the crown as the King’s heir.
If you are bewitched, you still take the crown.
Note: If the King is discarded faceup at the start of the selection
phase, randomly discard another character card faceup to
replace it and shuffle the King into the character deck.</string>

    <string name="EMPEROR_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Emperor</string>
    <string name="EMPEROR_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one gold for each noble district in your city.
At some point during your turn, you must take the crown from
the player who has it and give it to a different player, but not
yourself. You take either one gold from his stash or one card at
random from his hand. If he has neither gold in his stash nor
cards in hand, you do not take anything.
If you are killed, you skip your turn like any other character.
At the end of the round, reveal the Emperor’s character card
and, as the Emperor’s advisor, take the crown from the player
who has it and give it to a different player, but not yourself.
You do not take a resource from the new crowned player.
Note: If the Emperor is discarded faceup at the start of the
selection phase, randomly discard another character card faceup
to replace it and shuffle the Emperor into the character deck.
Note: The Emperor cannot be used in a 2-player game.</string>

    <string name="PATRICIAN_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Patrician</string>
    <string name="PATRICIAN_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one card for each noble district in your city.
At some point during your turn, you must take the crown. You
are now the crowned player, so you call characters for the rest of
the round, and you will be the first to choose a character during
the next round (until another player chooses the Patrician).
If you are killed, you skip your turn like any other character.
At the end of the round, reveal the Patrician’s character card
and take the crown as the Patrician’s heir.
If you are bewitched, you still take the crown.
Note: If the Patrician is discarded faceup at the start of the
selection phase, randomly discard another character card faceup
to replace it and shuffle the Patrician into the character deck.</string>

    <string name="BISHOP_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Bishop</string>
    <string name="BISHOP_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one gold for each religious district in your city.
During this round, the rank 8 character (Warlord, Diplomat, or
Marshal) cannot use its ability on your districts.
If you are killed, the rank 8 character can use its ability on your
districts. Similarly, if you are bewitched, the rank 8 character
cannot use its ability on the Witch’s districts, but it can use its
ability on the Bishop’s districts.</string>

    <string name="ABBOT_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Abbot</string>
    <string name="ABBOT_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain either one gold or one card for each religious
district in your city. You can choose any combination of the two
resources; for example, if you have three religious districts,
you can use this ability to gain three gold and zero cards, two
gold and one card, one gold and two cards, or zero gold and
three cards. You must declare the combination of resources you
wish to take before taking them.
If at any point during your turn you are not the player with the
most gold, the richest player must give you one gold from his
stash. If there is a tie for the richest player, choose which of
the tied players must give you one of his gold. If you are among
those tied for the richest player, you do not receive any gold.</string>

    <string name="CARDINAL_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Cardinal</string>
    <string name="CARDINAL_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one card for each religious district in your city.
If you want to build a district, but you do not have enough gold to
do so, you can take the remaining gold needed from one player.
For each gold you take, you must give that player one card from
your hand. Then you must pay to build that district in your city.
A player cannot deny you his gold, and you cannot take more
gold than is needed to build the intended district.</string>

    <string name="MERCHANT_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Merchant</string>
    <string name="MERCHANT_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one gold for each trade district in your city.
You gain one extra gold. You can use this ability regardless of
which resource you gathered this turn.</string>

    <string name="ALCHEMIST_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Alchemist</string>
    <string name="ALCHEMIST_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">At the end of your turn, you receive back all the gold you paid to
build districts this turn, but not gold you paid for other reasons
(such as the Smithy’s effect or the Tax Collector’s tax). This
effectively means that you can build districts “for free,” but only
if you would have had enough gold to build them.</string>

    <string name="TRADER_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Trader</string>
    <string name="TRADER_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one gold for each trade district in your city.
Trade districts do not count toward your building limit this
turn. This effectively means that you can build any number of
trade districts in addition to your building limit.</string>

    <string name="ARCHITECT_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Architect</string>
    <string name="ARCHITECT_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Gain two extra cards. You can use this ability regardless of
which resource you gathered this turn.
Your building limit this turn is three.</string>

    <string name="NAVIGATOR_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Navigator</string>
    <string name="NAVIGATOR_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain either four gold or four cards. You can use this ability
regardless of which resource you gathered this turn.
You cannot build any districts during your turn—not even
districts that do not count toward your building limit.</string>

    <string name="SCHOLAR_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Scholar</string>
    <string name="SCHOLAR_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Draw seven cards from the deck and choose one to add to your
hand. Shuffle the other six cards back into the district deck and
place it facedown in the center of the table.
Your building limit this turn is two.</string>

    <string name="WARLORD_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Warlord</string>
    <string name="WARLORD_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one gold for each military district in your city.
You can destroy one district of your choice by paying one fewer
gold than its building cost. So, you can destroy a one-cost
district for free, a two-cost district for one gold, a three-cost
district for two gold, and so on.
You cannot destroy a district in a completed city, but you
can destroy one of your own districts. Destroyed districts are
discarded facedown to the bottom of the district deck.</string>

    <string name="DIPLOMAT_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Diplomat</string>
    <string name="DIPLOMAT_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one gold for each military district in your city.
You can exchange one district in another player’s city for one
district in your city. If the other player’s district has a higher
cost than your district, you must give that player the difference
in gold from your stash. If your district has a higher cost than
the other player’s district, that player does not owe you any gold
in return.
You cannot exchange for a district in a completed city nor for
a district identical to a district already in your city, but you can
exchange one of your districts if you have a completed city.
Also, the district coming from your city cannot be identical to a
district already in the other player’s city.</string>

    <string name="MARSHAL_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Marshal</string>
    <string name="MARSHAL_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You gain one gold for each military district in your city.
You can seize one district with a building cost of three or less
in another player’s city by giving the owner gold equal to its
building cost. The seized district is added to your city.
You cannot seize a district in a completed city nor a district
identical to a district already in your city.</string>

    <string name="QUEEN_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Queen</string>
    <string name="QUEEN_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">If you are sitting next to the player who revealed the rank 4
character (King, Emperor, or Patrician), gain three gold. If
this character is sitting next to you, but has been killed by the
Assassin, you gain three gold when that card is revealed at the
end of the round.
Note: The Queen cannot be used in games with fewer than five
players.</string>

    <string name="ARTIST_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Artist</string>
    <string name="ARTIST_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">You can beautify up to two of your districts by assigning them
each one gold from your stash. The cost of a beautified district
is permanently increased by one, so a beautified district scores
one more point at the end of the game, the Warlord must pay
one more gold to destroy a beautified district, etc. (keep the
gold on the card as a reminder). A district can be beautified
only once.</string>

    <string name="TAXCOLLECTOR_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Tax Collector</string>
    <string name="TAXCOLLECTOR_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">When the Tax Collector is one of the characters in the game,
players are charged a property tax for building districts.
Immediately after a player builds a district, he places one gold
from his stash on the Tax Collector’s character token. This
applies even when a player builds a district that he has not paid
to build. If a player builds more than one district, he is charged
the property tax for each district built. If a player has no gold
remaining in his stash after building a district, he is not charged
a tax. The Tax Collector himself is not charged a tax.
At any time during your turn, you can take all gold from the Tax
Collector’s character token into your stash.
Even if the Tax Collector does not appear during a round
(because it was not chosen, it was discarded at the start of the
selection phase, or it was killed by the Assassin), players are
always charged a tax, and any gold left on the Tax Collector’s
token carries over to the next round.
In 2- and 3-player games, a player who chooses the Tax
Collector as one of his characters is still charged a tax for his
other character.
If the Magistrate confiscates a district from a player, the
Magistrate is charged the tax, not his target.</string>
</resources>
