<resources>
    <!--These are strings unique to Tic-Tac-Toe-->
    <string name="app_name">Citadels</string>
    <string name="hello_world">coffee is just bean soup</string>

    <string name="ASSASSIN_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Assassin</string>
    <string name="ASSASSIN_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">Call the name of another character whom you wish to kill.
        When the killed character is called to take his turn, he must
        remain silent and skip his entire turn for this round without
        revealing his character card.</string>

    <string name="WITCH_NAME" formatted="true" translatable="false">Witch</string>
    <string name="WITCH_DESC" formatted="true" translatable="false">First you must gather resources, then you must call the name
        of another character whom you wish to bewitch, and then your
        turn is put on hold. You cannot build at this time, and the only
        district effects you can use are those that occur when gathering
        resources (Gold Mine, Library, or Observatory).
        When the bewitched character is called to take his turn, he
        gathers resources and his turn immediately ends. He cannot
        build a district or use any of his character’s abilities—not even
        those that provide “extra” resources (like the Merchant’s extra
        gold). The only district effects that the bewitched player can
        use are those that occur when gathering resources.
        Now you resume your turn as if you were playing the bewitched
        character; you use that character’s abilities, including those that
        provide extra resources, passive abilities (such as the Bishop’s
        protection against rank 8 characters or the Architect’s increased
        building limit), and restrictions (such as the Navigator’s inability
        to build districts). You play with the cards in your hand, pay with
        the gold in your stash, gain resources from districts in your city,
        and build new districts in your city. You cannot use effects from
        unique districts owned by the bewitched player.
        If the Blackmailer is bewitched, you assign threat markers,
        receive bribes from threatened players, and choose to reveal the
        threat marker if the targeted player does not pay.
        If the King or Patrician is bewitched, he still takes the crown. If
        the Emperor is bewitched, you choose whom to give the crown
        to and take the resource from that player.</string>
</resources>
